[Music]
schwinn meridian adult tricycle 24 or 26
inchi wheel options low step through
aluminum frame
cargo basket multiple colors
designed with 26 inch wheels this bike
provides a comfortable ride
for those 5 foot 4 inches to 6 foot 2
inches in height the single speed
drivetrain is easy to use in
maintain linear pull brakes deliver
smooth and intuitive stopping and both
front and rear fenders
help keep clothing clean in damp weather
wide upright handlebars provide a stable
balanced ride
and the adjustable padded cruiser saddle
absorbs bumps super low stand over step
through
aluminum frame allows easy step through
access includes limited lifetime
warranty for as long as
you own the bike schwinn meridian adult
tricycle 24 or 26 inch wheel options low
step through aluminum frame
cargo basket multiple colors
schwinn is the best product you can
choice for your future